<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<game>
	<title>The Machine's Garden</title>

	<website>http://www.machinesgarden.com/</website>
	<based-in>Durham, North Carolina, United States</based-in>
	<press-can-request-copy>TRUE</press-can-request-copy>

	<socials>
		<social>
			<name>twitter.com/machinesgarden</name>
			<link>twitter.com/machinesgarden</link>
		</social>
	</socials>



	<description>
		Use the intelligence of a decommissioned military supercomputer to solve puzzles and guide the lives of humble villagers. Uncover the mystery of the Machine's Garden as you make your way through this short and challenging narrative-puzzle game.  Repair the Machine's forgotten subsystems, but beware the consequences. After centuries of dormancy, the military installation, vast and serpentine, has opened its eye.
	</description>

	<history>
		The Machines Garden is the first major release by developers Jon and Michael, based in North Carolina,  US.  The team decided to start development on The Machine's Garden after the success of their jam game, Snailboat in the first GMTK Game Jam. The Machines Garden is a passion project spanning nearly 3 years made in short bursts between major life events.
	</history>
	<features>
		<feature>Think critically to make your way through 35+ challenging and handcrafted hex grid puzzles</feature>
		<feature>Master the use of special cells that launch, attach and multiply hexes to solve puzzles</feature>
		<feature>Explore a poignant, yet lighthearted narrative through a series of slowly unraveling stories</feature>
		<feature>Immerse yourself in the atmospheric audio and visuals of the Machine's control room</feature>
	</features>


	<trailers>
		<trailer>
			<name>Gameplay Trailer</name>
			<youtube>p6xMH2sO8YQ</youtube>
		</trailer>

	</trailers>

	<credits>
		<credit>
			<person>Jon Miller</person>
			<role>Creative Lead, Engineering, Game Design, Art, Narrative</role>
		</credit>
		<credit>
			<person>Michael Schmitt</person>
			<website>https://twitter.com/toomuchtomato</website>
			<role>VFX, Audio, Puzzle Design, Publishing, Additional Code</role>
		</credit>
	</credits>

</game>
